Guide to the National Council of Jewish Women, Pittsburgh Section Records, 1894-2011 AIS.1964.40
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- NCJW Oral History Projects, 1967-2001; XXVIII.
  - Pittsburgh Section Project I: The Immigrant Experience, 1.
    - Burke, Ethel, March 23, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Burke, Nathan, March 23, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Caplan, Nettie, March 21, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Chaimovitz, Molly, November 2, 1969; Digital object includes interview with both Molly and Morris Chamovitz. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Chaimovitz, Morris, November 2, 1969; Digital content available with Molly Chaimovitz digital object. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Clair, Sarah, July 21, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Cody, Sam, February 9, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Cohen, Lena, January 9, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Nathan, November 18, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Coller, Victor, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Cowan, Jacob, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Robert, undated (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Dektor, Jacob, December 15, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Dizenfield, Sam, March 16, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Ellovich, Philip, November 2, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Feld, Philip, November 25, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Fink, Mrs. Morris, November 23, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Finkelpearl, Emma, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Finkelstein, Ann, March 9, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Forman, Abe, March 9, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Foreman, Esther, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Fried, William, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Friedland, Rae, December 1, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Friedman, Ethel, January 21, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Friedman, Florence, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Friedland, Mrs. William (Ida), August 1968 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Fuss, Sam, undated (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Gittleman, Fanny, February 4, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Glaser, Morris, October 6, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Glass, Max, January 15, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Glass, Neiman, undated (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Glick, Charles, March 11, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Goldberg, Abram, undated (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Goldblum, Hannah, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Goldenfeld, Martin, April 18, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Herman, December 11, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Gorn, Mrs. Albert, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Gottlieb, Lena, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Greenberg, Samuel, December 3, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Gusky, Esther, May 10, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Harris, Bess, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Hausman, David, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Hausman, Sophie, undated (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Herrup, Max, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Hirsch, Charles, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Horowitz, Mollie, February 5, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Horowitz, Rose, undated (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Isay, Albert, undated (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Iskowitz, Mamie, February 11, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Joseph, Abraham, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Josselson, Mary, undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Kahn, Gertrude, February 23, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Kasen, Bessie, undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Katz, Carl, December 16, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Nathan, October 22, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Katz, Pearl, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Katz, Sadie, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Katz, Samuel, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Kellmer, Bessie, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Kessler, Mrs. Louis, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Kimelman, Sabina, October 12, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Klahr, Morris, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Klarsfield, Henry, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Klein, Charles, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Kronick, Jacob, undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Kurtz, Sol, undated (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Lacov, Rose, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Latterman, Bertha, January 31, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Lencher, Benjamin, undated (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Lieber, Rose, July 1968 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Lieber, Sol, September 6, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Linder, Rose, October 28, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Lubov, Sam, undated (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Malakoff, Alice, June 1, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Malin, Gertrude, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Marsh, Rose, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Ruth, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Mazer, Minnie, March 6, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Melnick, Israel, October 24, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Menkel, Eugene, February 25, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Michaels, Israel, April 20, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Michaels, Mrs. L, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Leon, undated (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Minori, Emil, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Moskowitz, Izzy, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Needleman, Bertha, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Newman, Mrs. Nathan, undated (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Pearl, Morris, undated (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Pearlman, Ethel, undated (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Pearlman, Minnie, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Plotkin, Aaron, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Propper, Hyman, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Propper, Katie, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Protetch, Jacob, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Reichbaum, Abraham, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Reiser, Israel, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Rosenson, Helen, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Roth, Harry, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Roth, Morris, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Rudov, Rose, February 10, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Salzman, Esther, November 18, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Schugar, Charles, undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Schulman, George, undated (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Schutzberg, Louis, undated (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Schwartz, Frieda, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Schwartz, Sara, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Schwartz, Sophie, November 6, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Schweitzer, Harry, November 27, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Selzer, Ann (Mrs. Sam), January 29, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Shapira, Sarah, July 1968 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Shapiro, Jennie (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Sherman, Joseph (Jack), March 2, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Snyder, Rose, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Sobel, Rose, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Solomon, Abraham, December 17, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Solomon, Sarah, undated (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Spero, Mary, July 1968 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Spiegel, Sigmund, undated (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Surovitz, Jennie, February 14, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Swarz, Belle, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Tannenbaum, Max, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Tolchin, Sam, undated (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Topolsky, Bess, July 23, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Topolsky, Morris, January 10, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Topolsky, Henrietta (Yetta), January 8, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Twigg, Hilda, undated (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Unger, William, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Volkin, Nellie, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Weinberg, Martha, February 5, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Weiner, Nathan, October 31, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Weiner, William, February 11, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Weiss, Ralph, December 15, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Weissman, Saul, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Wolf, Morris, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Zeidenschneider, Annie, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Zupkoff, Ida, undated (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Zwang, Esther, undated (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Klein, Julia, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Data Analysis, Reports, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Data Analysis, Collation, Sections I-II, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Data Analysis, Collation, Sections II-III, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Data Analysis, Collation, Sections VI-VII, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Data Analysis, Collation, Sections VIII-XI, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Data Analysis, Collation, Sections XII-XIV, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - General Correspondence, Outgoing, 1968-1975 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, Incoming, 1968-1975 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - General Correspondence, Book Order Forms, 1968-1975 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence, Form Letters, 1968-1975 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Project Methodology (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Newsletters, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - News Releases, ca. 1969 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - By Myself I'm a Book. Manuscript A. (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - By Myself I'm a Book. Manuscript B. (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - By Myself I'm a Book, Manuscript C. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - By Myself I'm a Book, Manuscript D. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - By Myself I'm a Book. Introduction (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - By Myself I'm a Book. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Untitled, 1974 (Box 96, Video 1)
    - Aronson, Harry, October 11, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Abram, Ruben, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Israel, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Abromson, Keili, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Adelman, Alex, January 25, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Berkowitz, Bertha, August 26, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Berkowitz, Clara, November 22, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Chaitkin, Aaron, March 18, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Deemer, Nathan, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Drucker, Sonia, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Goldstein, Dora, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Green, Esther, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Greenberg, Esther Wool, November 20, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Jacobs, Harry, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Karsh, Rae (Mrs. Harry), November 8, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Katz, Leah, October 25, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Katz, Mrs. Nathan (Mollie), 1968 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Kramer, Lena, undated (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Langer, William, February 3, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - La Victoire, Dr. Freda, November 2, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Lebovitz, Eugene, July 8, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Lebovitz, Harry, November 24, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Leibovitz, Isadore, February 12, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Lerman, R., undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Leavitt, Frances, June 5, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Linder, Mrs., undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Lubow, Marsha (Mrs. Sam), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Mandel, Morris, October 30, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Marcus, Eva, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Meyerson, Alex, October 21, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Moravitz, Hyman, 1968; No folder exists. (Box 98, Folder 12A)
    - Moskov, Etta Roscow, February 24, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Morrison, Harry, April 1969 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Pare, Fannie, undated (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Peris, Fanny, 1969; Digital object includes interview with both Fanny and Hyman Peris. (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Peris, Hyman, 1969; Digital object includes interview with both Fanny and Hyman Peris. (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Robinson, Alex, undated (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Rogoff, Diana, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Rosen, Belle (Mrs. Mayer), October 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Rosen, Meyer, February 26, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Rothbart, Jacob, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Rothbart, Mrs. Pearl, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Rubinstein, Louis, January 4, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Saul, Joseph, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Simons, Doris, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Slawkin, Harry, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Snyder, Abe, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Snyder, Ann, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Solomon, Rose, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Stern, Sam, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Stollman, Anna, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Weinstein, Ruth, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Anonymous, undated (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - New Material Added, 2011
      - Recording of Recollections of the Jewish Aged Proposal, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - How We Did It: Methodological Considerations for an Oral History Project, 1968-1972 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - By Myself, I'm a Book Newspaper clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Questions to Ask Respondents, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Oral History Project I, various notes, reports, and correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Requests to purchase By Myself, I'm a Book, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and orders of By Myself, I'm a Book, 1970-1978 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Contract with Dr. Ailon Shiloh, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - Oral History Project I Publicity, 1971-1981 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - By Myself, I'm a Book mock up book jacket cover, ca.1972 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - By Myself, I'm a Book Reception slides, June 11, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - By Myself, I'm a Book remarks by Gene Dickman, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - Ida Cohen Selavan letter to the Jewish Chronicle regarding authorship of "By Myself, I'm a Book", 1973 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - Oral History Project I Respondents and Interviewers, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence regarding By Myself, I'm a Book, 1975-1977 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Oral History Project I tapes deposit at the Archives of Industrial Society, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - "The Jewish Immigrant Experience" Duquesne University History Forum Program Presentation, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Section Project II: My Voice was Heard, 2.
    Beginning in 1974, the NCJW Pittsburgh Section conducted a second oral history project focusing on the impact Pittsburgh's Jewish community made locally, nationally, and internationally. The project continued through the 1990s and added 350 oral histories. Some individuals were interviewed a second time. Material added in 2011 can be found under the section "New Material Added."
    - Aaron, Marcus Lester, 1975; 1 cassette tape (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Aaron, Maxine Goldmark, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Sarah Davis, December 1, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Abrams, Solomon, May 19, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Adelsheim, Silas, November 1, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Alber, Freda, February 4, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Albert, Anne Steinhardt, March 27, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Anathan, Bessie Frank, March 4, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Apt, Joan Frank, August 22, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Arkus, Jane Callomon, July 13, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Arkus, Leon Anthony (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Arkus, Leon Anthony, December 11, 1978
      - Arkus, Leon Anthony, 1992
    - Arnheim, Stanley, April 1, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, Charlotte, December 1, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Atlas, Paula, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Balter, Beatrice S. (Bobbi), December 10, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Barach, Edna Levy, November 3, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Baskin, Philip, April 29, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Benswanger, Eleanor Dreyfus, September 11, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Berger, Meyer (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - Berger, Meyer, July 14, 1982
      - Berger, Meyer, undated
    - Bergman, Sidney M., March 8, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Berkman, Allen, August 21, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Berkman, Selma (Box 100, Folder 22)
      - Berkman, Selma, 1988
      - Berkman, Selma, July 25, 1992
    - Binstock, Doris D., October 20, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Binstock, Dorothy, September 4, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Binstock, Tessie, February 24, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Berman, Rebecca, January 15, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Bleiberg, Morris, July 11, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - Block, William, May 10, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - Bloom, Albert W., May 3, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 29)
    - Bloom, Evelyn G., February 19, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - Bluestone, Max, June 5, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - Blumenthal, Dorothy, 1973, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - Blumstein, Alfred, April 5, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - Borke, Mitchell L., April 19, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - Breskin, Joseph, November 5, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - Brunwasser, Albert, January 28, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 36)
    - Buncher, Jack, May 26, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 37)
    - Busis, Sidney, Dr., January 14, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 38)
    - Butler, Chantze, February 20, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 39)
    - Butler, Donald, May 12, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 40)
    - Caplan, Gertrude F., 1989, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 41)
    - Caplan, Jerry, May 2, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 42)
    - Caplan, Louis, June 1976 (Box 100, Folder 43)
    - Caplan, Paul S., Dr., May 3, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Chait, Ida, November 19, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Chotiner, Henrietta, January 13, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Charlotte, June 7, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Fannie, March 1, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Jesse, 1995; No folder exists. (Box 101, Folder 5A)
    - Cohen, Paul, November 8, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Stanley G., March 8, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Colker, James, September 30, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Comay, Amos, February 24, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Copeland, Ann, May 6, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Cowan, Barton Z., January 6, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Crantz, David Milton, May 9, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Criep, Dr. Leo H. (Leo Hermann), November 11, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Cuden, Helen, February 16, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Damick, Marian, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Dora, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Jacob, April 27, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Jean L., October 7, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Laura Adolph, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - DeRoy, Mayer, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Diamond, Hyman, August 28, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Dickman, Gene, April 10, 2000; May 5, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Dinman, Bertram David, Dr., 1994 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Dorian, Frederick, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Eaton, Joseph W., Dr., May 13, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Edelstein, Jason Z., Rabbi, November 29, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Edlis, Jerome, November 2, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Elbaum, Nathan, November 18, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Elbling, Gloria, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Elkind, Sue Saniel, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Elkus, Leonore R., May 9, 1983; June 14, 1983; October 25, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Ellenbogen, Rae, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Epstine, Harry, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Epstine, Jane, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - Falk, Katherine Sonneborn, June 19, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - Falk, Leon, June 14, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - Fenves, Steven, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Fine, Milton, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Fineberg, Herman, March 18, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Fienberg, Jacob, February 16, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Feingold, Bess, February 20, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - Finegold, Marcella, April 9, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Finegold, Wilfred J., 1982 (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Finkel, Elliot, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Finkelhor, Dorothy C. and Lawrence Herbert, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 45)
    - Finkelhor, Marion, Judge, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 46)
    - Fischer, Ben (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Fischer, Ben, 1977
      - Fischer, Ben, 1993
    - Fisher, Bernard, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Fisher, Edwin R., Dr., 1997 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Fisher, Myrtle M., 1975 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Fleischman, Justin, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Forscher, Frederick, Dr., 1988 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Frank, James A., 1975 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Frank, Nancy Newman, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Frank, Ruth O., 1996, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Freehof, Lillian S. (Lillian Simon), 1975 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Freehof, Solomon Bennett, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Freund, Louise, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Friedberg, Joan Brest, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Friedberg, Lillian A. (Lillian Adlow), 1973 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Friedberg, Simeon A., 1996 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Friedman, Janice, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Frumerman, Pauline Marks, Dr., 1976 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Frumerman, Robert, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Gefsky, Meyer (Buck), 1975 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Goldberg, Bernard, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Goldberg, Irwin, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Goldberg, Marcella Cohen, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Goldman, Foster, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - Goldstein, Lillian, 2000 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Goldstein, Maurice, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - Goldstein, Samuel J., 1989 (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - Goodman, Bernard, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - Gordon, Herman, Dr., 1989 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Gould, Rita J., 1997 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Grauer, Juliette, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Green, Benjamin, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - Greenberger, Blanche, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - Gross, Sidney, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - Gruber, Aaronel DeRoy, May 11, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 34)
    - Hailperin, Celia Moss, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 35)
    - Half, Ivan, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 36)
    - Halpern, Bernard, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 37)
    - Hamberg, Lester A., 1987 (Box 102, Folder 38)
    - Harrison, Myrtle, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 39)
    - Harrison, Roland, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 40)
    - Haskell, Jane, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 41)
    - Herskovitz, Ruth Gordon, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 42)
    - Hartz, Rose, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 43)
    - Hast, Julian, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 44)
    - Heber, Leon (Leib), 1979 (Box 102, Folder 45)
    - Hepner, Betty, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 46)
    - Heppenheimer, Bella, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 47)
    - Hirsch, Burton, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 48)
    - Hirsh, Pauline, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 49)
    - Hoffman, Gertrude, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 50)
    - Holstein, Lillian, January 24, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 51)
    - Isaacs, Flora M., June 1987 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Isenstein, Irma, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Itkin, Ivan, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Alexander, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Jacob, Irene, November 16, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Jacob, Walter, Rabbi, July 22, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Jaffe, Arthur Heilman, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Jandorf, Robert, November 7, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Jena, Milton, Dr., November 5, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Jonas, Hans, October 27, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Kahn, Joseph (Ziggy), December 19, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Kamin, Harry, March 16, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Kaplan, Bernard, January 17, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Kaplan, Lawrence, Judge, January 4, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Kaplan, Natalie A., 1998 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Karp, Richard, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Katz, Bessie, July 16, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Katz, Harry L., June 18, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Katz, Joseph M., 1979 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Kaufman, Sam, undated; No folder exists. (Box 103, Folder 19A)
    - Kaufman, Nathan, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Kaufmann, Oliver M., December 16, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Kavaler, Mina, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Kavaler, Vigdor W., October 2, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Kent, Allen, May 12, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Kessler, Aharon, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Kessler, Laibe, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Kimel, Hyman, July 19, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Kingsbaker, Caroline, June 3, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Klein, Claire, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 29)